Guide to the Jewish Heritage Foundation of North Carolina Oral History Collection, 1981-2014 RL.11031
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Durham and surrounding areas, 1981; 1986-2008; 2014; undated; 3
  - Rapport, Leonard (Durham / Chapel Hill / Asheville), 1987; 88
    - Leonard Rapport. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project, 1987 September 9; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Ray, Lois, 1997; 89
    - Lois Ray. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project, 1997 May 12; audiocassette (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-031)
      Container label: "Lois Ray"
  - Rogoff, Leonard, circa 2008
    - Leonard Rogoff. Interviewed by Steven Channing for Durham: a self-portrait (documentary film) and Down Home project, circa 2008; digital betacam (Box 7, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-030)
  - Rosenzweig, Efraim, Rabbi, 1986; 90
    - Rabbi Efraim Rosenzweig. Interviewed by Irene Zipper for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 June 22; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-089, Digital-materials RL11031-SET-0001, Audio-file rl11031_cs_089_001.wav)
      Container label: "Rabbi Rosenzweig Oral History/Jewish Community"
  - Sager, Steven, Rabbi, 1986; 91
    - Rabbi Steven Sager. Interviewed by Sheldon Hanft and Leonard Rogoff, 1986 September 01?; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-071)
      Container label: "Steven Sager"
  - Schultzberg, Alvin (Chapel Hill), 1992; 92
    - Alvin Schultzberg. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project, 1992 April 21; notes (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Segal, May, 1986; 93
    - May Segal. Interviewed by Mollie Fridovich for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 April 1; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-051)
      Container label: "Interview with May Segal April 1, 1986"
    - May Segal. Interviewed by Mollie Fridovich for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 April 1; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Shimm, Melvin "Mel", 1986; 94
    - Melvin "Mel" Shimm. Interviewed by Robin Gruber for Duke University oral history seminar, 1986 January 29; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-062)
      Container label: "Mel Shimm"
    - Melvin "Mel" Shimm. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 December 15; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-048)
    - Melvin "Mel" Shimm. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 December 15; transcript (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Slifkin, Miriam, undated; 95
    - Miriam Slifkin. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff, undated; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-115)
      Container label: "Miriam Slifkin"
  - Stadiem, Abe, 1992; 96
    - Abe Stadiem. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project, 1992 April 8; audiocassette (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-146)
      Container label: "Abe Stadiem"
    - Abe Stadiem. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project, 1992 April 8; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Stahl, Helen, circa 1986; 97
    - Helen Stahl. Interviewed by Violet Tartell for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, circa 1986; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-113)
      Container label: "Helen Stahl (1955)"
  - Swartz, Max, 1985-1986; 98
    - Max Swartz. Interviewed by Nina Shubert and Robert Klein for Beth El Synagogue Confirmation class project, 1986 April 1; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-072)
      Container label: "Max Swartz/Nina Shubert/Robert Klein"
    - Max Swartz. Interviewed by Robin Gruber for Duke University oral history seminar, 1985 December 4; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-073)
      Container label: "Max Swartz "
    - Max Swartz. Interviewed by Robin Gruber for Duke University oral history seminar, 1985 December 4; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Tuchman, Louis, Rabbi, 1994; 99
    - Rabbi Louis Tuchman. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project, 1994 April 12; audiocassette (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-163)
      Container label: "Rabbis/Ornstein"
    - Rabbi Louis Tuchman. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project, 1994 April 12; transcript (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Wishnov, Hazel Gladstein, 1986; 1992; 100
    - Hazel Gladstein Wishnov. Interviewed by Robin Gruber for Duke University oral history seminar, 1986 February 12; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-077)
      Container label: "Hazel Wishnov"
    - Hazel Gladstein Wishnov. Interviewed by Robin Gruber for Duke University oral history seminar, 1986 February 12; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Ethel Mae Bernson and Hazel Gladstein Wishnov. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project, 1992 April 27; audiocassette (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-166)
      Container label: "[Untitled]"
    - Ethel Mae Bernson and Hazel Gladstein Wishnov. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project, 1992 April 27; transcript (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Yoffie, Eric, Rabbi, 1986; 101
    - Rabbi Eric Yoffie. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 July 21; transcript (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Fayetteville and surrounding areas, 1998-2008; undated; 4
  Geographic locations represented in this series include Fayetteville and Lumberton, North Carolina.
  - Evans, Monroe, circa 2006; 102
    - Monroe Evans. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, circa 2006; digital betacam (Box 7, Video-cassette RL10159-Dbcam-028)
    - Monroe Evans. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, circa 2006; transcript (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Evans, Mildred, circa 2006; 103
    - Mildred Evans. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, circa 2006; digital betacam (Box 7, Video-cassette RL10159-Dbcam-028)
    - Mildred Evans. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, circa 2006; transcript (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Fleishman, Joel, 2005; 104
    - Joel Fleishman. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2005 July 14; digital betacam (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-003)
      Container label: "Joel Fleishman"
    - Joel Fleishman. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2005 July 14; transcript (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Fleishman, Harriet and Michael, undated; 105
    - Harriet and Michael Fleishman. Interviewed by unknown interviewer, undated; transcript (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Ucko, Henry, Rabbi, circa 1998; 106
    - Rabbi Henry Ucko. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Migrations project, circa 1998; transcript (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Weinstein, David (Lumberton), 2008; 107
    - David Weinstein. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2008 August 5; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-076)
      Container label: "David Weinstein"
    - David Weinstein. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2008 August 5; transcript (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Goldsboro and surrounding areas, 1998-2007; undated; 5
  Geographic locations represented in this series include Goldsboro, Greenville, Kinston, Rocky Mount, and Wilson, North Carolina.
  - Brody, Morris (Greenville, NC), circa 1998; 108
    - Morris Brody. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Migrations project, circa 1998; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-116)
      Container label: "Morris Brody, Michael Caine, Greenville, SC [NC], Bad Audio"
  - Cain, Michael, Rabbi (Greenville, NC), circa 1998; 109
    - Rabbi Michael Cain. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Migrations project, circa 1998; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-116)
    - Rabbi Michael Cain. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Migrations project, circa 1998; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-129)
      Container label: "Rabbi Cain, Greenville"
    - Rabbi Michael Cain. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Migrations project, circa 1998; transcript (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Hanchrow, Flora (Wilson), circa 1998; 110
    - Flora Hanchrow. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Migrations project, circa 1998; audiocassette (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-150)
      Container label: "Flora Hanchrow/Linda Silverstein"
  - Kanter, Jerry and Sharon (Kinston), 2005; 111
    - Jerry and Sharon Kanter. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2005 December 5; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-108)
      Container label: "Jerry Kanter"
    - Jerry and Sharon Kanter. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2005 December 5; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Krumbein, Amy Meyers, 1999; 112
    - Amy Meyers Krumbein. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Migrations project, 1999 January 11; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-118)
      Container label: "Amy Meyers Crumbein [Krumbein]"
  - Fuerst, Dale and Herbert (Rocky Mount), circa 1998; 113
    - Dale and Herbert Fuerst. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Migrations project, circa 1998; transcript (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Leder, Arnold, 2007; 114
    - Arnold Leder. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 March 21; digital betacam (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-011)
      Container label: "Oheb Temple, Goldsboro: Arnold Leder & Pete Norris, Emily Weil"
  - Leder, Steven (Wilson), 2007; 115
    - Steven Leder. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 March 21; audiocassette (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-010)
      Container label: "Steven Leder"
    - Steven Leder. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 March 21; transcript (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Steven Leder. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 March 22; digital betacam (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-012)
      Container label: "Goldsboro: Emily Weil, downtown exteriors, Steve Leder - Wilson"
    - Steven Leder. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 March 22; digital betacam (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-013)
      Container label: "Steve Leder - Wilson - band"
  - Levin, Richard (Williamston), 2006; 116
    - Richard Levin. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 March 10; audiocassette (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-020)
      Container label: "Richard Levin "
    - Richard Levin. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 March 10; transcript (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Norris, Pete, Pastor, 2007; 117
    - Pastor Pete Norris. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 March 21; digital betacam (Box 7, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-011)
  - Oettinger, Elmer (Wilson / Chapel Hill), undated; 118
    - Elmer Oettinger. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff, undated; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-081)
      Container label: "Elmer Oettinger"
  - Shrago, Bill (Goldsboro / Rocky Mount), circa 2000; 119
    - Bill Shrago. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Migrations project, circa 2000; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-063)
      Container label: "Shrago"
    - Bill Shrago. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Migrations project, circa 2000; transcript (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Weil, Emily, 2007; 120
    - Emily Weil. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 March 21; digital betacam (Box 7, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-011)
    - Emily Weil. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 March 21; digital betacam (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-012)
- Greensboro and surrounding areas, 1998-2008; 6
  Geographic locations represented in this series include Burlington, Greensboro, and High Point, North Carolina.
  - Asher, Raphael, Rabbi, 2007; 121
    - Rabbi Raphael Asher. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 October 22; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Bernard, Zelda (High Point), 2006; 122
    - Zelda Bernard. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 March 8; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-079)
      Container label: "Zelda Bernard"
    - Zelda Bernard. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 March 8; transcript (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Bluethenthal, Arthur and Joanne, 2005; 123
    - Arthur and Joanne Bluethenthal. Interviewed by Sarah Malido for Down Home project, 2005 June 29; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-056)
      Container label: "Art & Joan [Joanne] Bluethenthal"
    - Arthur and Joanne Bluethenthal. Interviewed by Sarah Malido for Down Home project, 2005 June 29; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-057)
  - Bluethenthal, Arthur and Joanne, 2005; 124
    - Arthur and Joanne Bluethenthal. Interviewed by Sarah Malido for Down Home project, 2005 June 29; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Cone, Benjamin, Jr., 2007; 125
    - Benjamin Cone, Jr.. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 November 26; digital betacam (Box 7, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-026)
      Container label: "Ben Cone - exteriors - hunting - interview"
  - Elsewhere Artist Collaborative interns and resident artists, 2007; 126
    - Elsewhere Artist Collaborative interns and resident artists. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff with additional video footage for Down Home project, 2007 June 18; digital betacam (Box 7, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-017)
      Interviewees include George Scheer, Lisa Lipton, Cynthia Brinich-Langlois, Saralee Gallien, Jarema Osofsky, Yuko Takemura, and Eliza Wicks-Frank. Container label: "Charlotte: Jubans; Greensboro: Elsewhere Artist Collaborative"
  - Gray, Sidney and David, 2007; 127
    - Sidney and David Gray. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 September 20; digital betacam (Box 7, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-024)
      Container label: "Greensboro: Samet interviews: Norm, Harry, Lenny, Gray interviews: Sid, David, Elsewhere"
  - Guttman, Fred, Rabbi, 2007; 128
    - Rabbi Fred Guttman. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 October 9; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-042)
      Container label: "Rabbi Fred Guttman"
    - Rabbi Fred Guttman. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 October 9; transcript (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Hamburger, Dorothy, 2005; 129
    - Dorothy Hamburger. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2005; audiocassette (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-169)
  - Israel, Adelaide, 2002; 130
    - Adelaide Israel. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2002 October 30; betacam-sp (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Bcam-007)
      Container label: "NC Jewish History, Interview Carolyn LeBauer, Adelaide Israel - beg. Int."
    - Adelaide Israel. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2002 October 30; betacam-sp (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Bcam-008)
      Container label: "NC Jewish History, Interview Carolyn LeBauer, Adelaide Israel"
    - Adelaide Israel. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2002 October 30; betacam-sp (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Bcam-009)
      Container label: "Interview: Adelaide Israel Tape I"
    - Adelaide Israel. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2002 October 30; betacam-sp (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Bcam-010)
      Container label: "Interview: Adelaide Israel Tape II"
    - Adelaide and Archie Israel. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2002 October 30?; betacam-sp (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Bcam-011)
      Container label: "Interview Adelaide Israel/Archie Israel"
    - Adelaide and Archie Israel. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2002 October 30?; transcript (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Israel, Archie, 2002; 132
    - Adelaide and Archie Israel. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2002 October 30?; betacam-sp (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Bcam-011)
    - Adelaide and Archie Israel. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2002 October 30?; transcript (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Kaplan, Arthur (High Point), 2005; 133
    - Arthur Kaplan. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2005 August 1; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-137)
      Container label: "Arthur Kaplan"
  - Kaplan, Leonard (Greensboro / High Point), 2008; 134
    - Leonard Kaplan. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2008 June 5; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-144)
      Container label: "Leonard Kaplan"
    - Leonard Kaplan. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2008 June 5; transcript (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Labell, Nat, 2005; 135
    - Nat Labell. Interviewed by Natalie Mapou for Down Home project, 2005 April 19; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-068)
      Container label: "Nat Labell - Greensboro, 4/19/05"
    - Nat Labell. Interviewed by Natalie Mapou for Down Home project, 2005 April 19; transcript (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - LeBauer, Carolyn, 2002; 136
    - Carolyn LeBauer. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2002 October 30; betacam-sp (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Bcam-007)
    - Carolyn LeBauer. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2002 October 30; betacam-sp (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Bcam-008)
    - Carolyn LeBauer. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2002 October 30; transcript (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - LeBauer, Eugene, Joe, and Sam, 2008; 137
    - Eugene, Sam, and Joe LeBauer. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2008 January 1; audiocassette (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-174)
  - Levin, Seymour (Burlington / Greensboro), 2007; 138
    - Seymour Levin. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 December 24; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-085)
      Container label: "Seymour Levin"
    - Seymour Levin. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 December 24; transcript (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Levin, Sol, 2007; 139
    - Sol Levin. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 October 25; notes (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Parish, Lucy Goldsmith (Greensboro / Mount Airy), 2005; 140
    - Lucy Goldsmith Parish. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2005 May 29; audiocassette (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-003)
      Container label: "Lucy Goldsmith Parish"
  - Roth, Betty, 2005; 141
    - Betty Roth. Interviewed by Natalie Mapou for Down Home project, 2005 April 28; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-070)
      Container label: "Betty Roth"
    - Betty Roth. Interviewed by Natalie Mapou for Down Home project, 2005 April 28; transcript (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Sabbah, Maurice - American Hebrew Academy, circa 2002-2003; 142
    - Maurice "Chico" Sabbah. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, circa 2002-2003; betacam-sp (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Bcam-005)
      Container label: "American Hebrew Academy - northern man on oxygen [Chico Sabbah]- 2nd tape?"
    - Maurice "Chico" Sabbah. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, circa 2002-2003; betacam-sp (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Bcam-006)
      Container label: "American Hebrew Academy - administrator"
    - Maurice "Chico" Sabbah. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, circa 2002-2003; betacam-sp (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Bcam-012)
      Container label: "American Hebrew Academy - Saba [Sabbah], administrator"
    - Maurice "Chico" Sabbah. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, circa 2002-2003; betacam-sp (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Bcam-013)
      Container label: "Chico Sabbah"
    - Maurice "Chico" Sabbah., circa 2002-2003; transcript (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Samet, Elsie (Greensboro / High Point), 2006; 143
    - Elsie Samet. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 November 15; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-069)
      Container label: "Elsie Samet"
    - Elsie Samet. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 November 15; transcript (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Samet, Joan Klein (Greensboro / High Point), 2006; 146
    - Joan Klein Samet. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 July 17; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-090)
      Container label: "Samet [V? J?]"
    - Joan Klein Samet. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 July 17; transcript (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Joan Klein Samet and Harry Samet. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 July 17; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-117)
      Container label: "Samet "
    - Joan Klein Samet and Harry Samet. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 July 17; index (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Joan Klein Samet and Harry Samet. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 July 17; transcript (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Samet, Harry (Greensboro / High Point), 2006-2007; 147
    - Joan Klein Samet and Harry Samet. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 July 17; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-117)
    - Joan Klein Samet and Harry Samet. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 July 17; index (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Joan Klein Samet and Harry Samet. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 July 17; transcript (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Norman, Harry, and Lenny Samet. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 September 20; digital betacam (Box 7, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-024)
    - Norman, Harry, and Lenny Samet. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 September 20; DVD (Box 6, Video-disc RL11031-DVD-001)
      Container label: "Down Home: Jewish life in North Carolina: Norman Samet, Harry Samet, Lenny Samet, Greensboro, NC"
  - Samet, Leonard, 2007; 148
    - Norman, Harry, and Lenny Samet. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 September 20; digital betacam (Box 7, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-024)
    - Norman, Harry, and Lenny Samet. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 September 20; DVD (Box 6, Video-disc RL11031-DVD-001)
  - Samet, Norman, 2007; 149
    - Norman, Harry, and Lenny Samet. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 September 20; digital betacam (Box 7, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-024)
    - Norman, Harry, and Lenny Samet. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 September 20 (Box 6, Video-disc RL11031-DVD-001)
  - Scheer, George (Elsewhere Artist Collaborative), 2007; 150
    - George Scheer. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 June 18; digital betacam (Box 7, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-017)
  - Silver, Louis, 2007; 151
    - Louis Silver. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 December 11; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-101)
      Container label: "Louis Silver Greensboro 12/12/07"
    - Louis Silver. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 December 11; transcript (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Silverstein, Linda, circa 1998; 152
    - Linda Silverstein. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Migrations project, circa 1998; audiocassette (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-150)
  - Sloan, Frank and Thomas, 2007; 153
    - Frank and Thomas Sloan. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 December 14; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-098)
      Container label: "Tom & Frank Sloan"
    - Frank and Thomas Sloan. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 December 14; transcript (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Swartzberg, Fred (High Point), 2004; 154
    - Fred Swartzberg. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2004 July 11; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-074)
      Container label: "Fred Swartzberg interview 7/11/2004"